DAVID K. BROWN

6495 Yellow Birch Street, Cumming, GA 30040 (256) 520-0003 • GaTech55@gmail.com
GitHub • Portfolio

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Salesforce Business Analyst with recognized strengths in reporting using Power BI, SAP Business Objects and Tibco Spotfire. Ten plus years' experience in Healthcare IT Operations. Deep technical expertise and solution-oriented approach to issues using knowledge gained from certifications in Salesforce, ITIL and Lean Six Sigma. Detailed understanding of contract management, knowledge management, entitlements, and reporting. Highly knowledgeable in Salesforce.com, SAP ECC&CRM, and ServiceNow. Currently participating in the Georgia Tech Professional Education Coding Boot Camp with a projected completion date of 2/2021.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Administrator/Business Analyst

April 2019 – Present

Ingenious Med - Atlanta, GA

- ♦ In less than 2 months from start date obtained Salesforce Administrator certification
- Responsible for the configuration, reporting, training, support, maintenance and overall improvement of Ingenious Med's instance of Salesforce.com
- ♦ Collaborated directly with sales, marketing, implementations, integrations, support and C-Suite leaders to ensure satisfaction with the systems/process remained high
- Automated Incident Requests which contributed to 430 hours of time savings in 2019 and 230 hours in 2020
- Created 20+ Power BI Dashboards used by C-Suite daily along with Account Management, Product Management and Operations Excellence teams
- Simplified/Automated Mid-Year and Annual Survey process used to generate NPS scores for Ingenious Med
- ♦ Identified company-wide historic SLA entitlement tracking error and led the rework of entire entitlement system
- Created two custom methods for tracking stopped time for support cases
- Advised interns in the creation of Salesforce community intranet and maintained Apex code/Visualforce pages

Services Business Analyst

October 2017 - April 2019

Allscripts Healthcare Solutions, Inc – Alpharetta, GA

- Responsible for creating business value for Allscripts and its customers through understanding data environment, designing data strategies, performing extracts, transforms, load activities, and operationalizing models
- Worked closely with team members and business partners to interpret data while implementing solutions that captured value for the business
- Significant impact to Business Unit (BU) with creation of automated Power BI dashboards which resulted in an estimated time savings of 872 hours/month for the year 2018
- Assisted with Allscripts' implementation of ServiceNow
- Supported the transition of McKesson acquisition from SAP CRM to the newly implemented ServiceNow tool
- Took initiative to personally purchase training classes for Power BI, DAX and SQL which led to becoming the SME for Power BI
- Overcame initial challenges related to the creation of Senior Leadership Operations deck as well as trained coworkers on the new process
- Led collaboration and creation of the Support dashboard which 120 managers used daily
- Provided onsite training to the customer facing Client Account Management team in the use of the dashboard for external business reviews
- Initiated the creation of the internal Innovation Team which was used to help drive synergy and locate potential time saving opportunities
- During my performance review the ability to build relationships with business leaders and teams was identified by my manager as my greatest strength

Business Intelligence Analyst

November 2014 – September 2017

McKesson Corporation - Alpharetta, GA

- ♦ Promoted into the Managed Services Organization to create an organization scorecard within Business Objects
- Created and maintained the largest number of Business Objects reports within McKesson Corporation
- Automated 11 major reports with an estimated time savings of 112 days/year for the EIS BU
- Primary focus of reports tied to customer attrition, team utilization, capacity reports, scorecards & KPIs
- ♦ Leveraged the 4 Disciplines of Execution strategy to create a Customer Commitment report for BU's Wildly Important Goal
- ♦ Assisted in the creation and monthly production of the Exec Leadership PowerPoint and LRP reports for BU
- ◆ Team Lead for the offshore report development team consisting of 4 contractors in India and South America (65 completed requests)

Business Systems Analyst 3 – McKesson Technology Solutions

August 2013 – September 2014

McKesson Corporation - Alpharetta, GA

- Promoted to BSA position in newly created "Program and Release Management Portfolio" team
- Managed 120 existing Business Requests and implemented new Business Request process for SAP CRM throughout the organization
- ♦ Led a team of 50+ Subject Matter Experts from 5 BUs in identifying enhancements, defects, prioritizing requests, requirements gathering and submission of Business Requests to the Clarity tracking tool
- Created and maintained Business Objects reports for leadership related to Net Promoter Scores, Time Tracking, Service Order analysis, and Remedy ticket creation/aging
- ♦ Used the Service Enhancement Delivery Model (SEDM) to prioritize scope of work to ensure optimal level of service for the stakeholders through efficient use of technology solutions
- Conducted and assisted with requirements gathering, User Acceptance Testing, Unit Test Planning and Solution Verification within Development and Quality environments
- Selected for special projects related to Export Control (ECCN) and Medical Device identification for regulatory purposes
- Provided application support and training within SAP CRM GUI using a range of processes to improve internal and external experiences
- ♦ Inherited Team Lead and Tier 2/3 responsibilities from the previous Product Support Rep position

Product Support Rep 3 – McKesson Technology Solutions

May 2009 - July 2013

McKesson Corporation – Alpharetta, GA ('09-'10 contracted through Agile Resources, Inc)

- ◆ Team Lead responsible for supporting and managing 25,000+ McKesson/RelayHealth Customer Portal, Knowledge Base (KNOVA), and Internet Customer Self Service (ICSS) accounts
- Created SAP CRM Best Practice Policy adopted by multiple BUs. This policy corrected more than 1,000 duplicate Business Partner accounts
- Generated monthly reports compiling raw data from Business Objects into charts and graphs to analyze support incident trends
- Identified issues and tested solutions for numerous problems related to support of SAP CRM including Regression and User Acceptance Testing
- ♦ Identified as a resource for the CRM Discovery Task Force and recognized as a SAP Super User Level 1
- ♦ Download Central (DLC) Administrator responsible for creating accounts, members, and entitlements in the DLC database
- Knowledge Champion and KNOVA administrator responsible for creating products, users, customer accounts, and Microsites in the Knowledge Base environment
- ♦ SharePoint Administrator, Communications Co-Lead, and Technology Co-Lead of Knowledge Exchange (KnEx) program

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Salesforce Administrator

Microsoft SharePoint Site Administrator SAP Business Objects Enterprise XI 12.1.0

SAP CRM 7.0 ENHP2 SP6 (GUI, CP1, CQA, CDA)

SQL Server Management Studio

Microsoft Power BI (DAX & SQL)

Aptean Knowledge Management Solution Platform 7.3

ServiceNow

BMC Remedy AR System

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery

Progressive Web Apps Agile Methodology

Agrie Metriodolog

Bootstrap

React.js, Express.js, Node.js

MongoDB

MySql

Command Line

Git

CERTIFICATIONS / PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

Georgia Tech Professional Education – Coding Boot Camp (expected 2/2021)

Salesforce Administrator (2019)

Lean Six Sigma Yellow Belt Certification (2019)

ServiceNow Performance Analytics Advanced training (2018)

Microsoft SQL 20461D training (2017)

Georgia Tech Professional Education - McKesson Learning Excellence Acceleration Program (2014)

Aptean Knowledge Management: Administrator Boot Camp (2012)

ITIL v3 Foundation Certification (2011)

Aptean Knowledge Management: Universal Metadata (2011)

EDUCATION

2004-2008

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, Georgia

Bachelor of Science, Management; Concentration in Information Technology and Operations